我们已经努力了三个小时了
We have been at this for three hours.
搅拌奶油到底要多长时间啊
How long does it take to churn butter?
很明显至少要花三个小时
Well, obviously it takes at least three hours!
我很抱歉  布丽  我只是
I'm sorry, bree, I just...
我真的很想要那些树皮做的项链玩意儿
I really want one of those bark necklace thingies.
好了  我们来看看
Okay, let's check.
哈  哈  给你们看看  女士们
Ha ha! in yo face, ladies!
你 你看见那个了 对不
You-- you saw that, right?
我们还能够记上分么
We're still going to get credit for that?
不能
No.
但是伐木比赛又诞生了一个赢家哦
But we do have a winner in the wood-chopping competition.
祝贺鲁尼队
Congratulations, team rooney!
太好了
Yes!
伐木的秘诀就是痛恨那块木头
The secret is to really hate the wood.
妈
Mom.
今年终于属于我们了
This is finally our year.
我的意思是  我们这么领先
I mean, we are so far ahead,
都已经拿定那个金搅子了
We've got that golden butter churn all locked up.
但是  除非我们干了什么傻事
Well, unless we do something dumb--
我说的我们  是指你  所以最好什么都别碰
And by we, I mean you-- so don't touch anything.
嘿  听着你说呢  妈妈
Hey, I hear you, mom.
所以这里
So here...
就是通往金搅子的大道
Is to the golden butter churn.
麦蒂·鲁尼
Maddie rooney.
你是不是刚刚喝了一口又绵又滑的白水
Did you just take a nice, long drink of water
来防止脱水呢
To avoid dehydration?
对的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
那么你就死掉啦
Then you're dead.
呃 什么 这
Uh-- wha-- uh...
等一下 先别
Wait, hold on.
我煮沸了这水啊
I boiled this water.
不不不不  你煮的是那桶水
No no no no. you boiled that water.
啧啧
Oops!
但我们今年势在必得啊
But we were going to win this year.
把死人抬出去
Bringing out the dead!
这  不  妈妈  我都是很小心的
Wha-- no, mom, I have been so careful.
你懂得  我们那么领先
You know what-- we are so far ahead,
你单枪匹马就能把金搅子赢回来
You win that golden butter churn for both of us!
你要让梦想成真啊
You keep this dream alive!
把尸体准备展览吧
Let's prepare the body for the viewing.
奇异恩典
amazing grace
何等
how sweet...